dsm-publishing.com 2013-06-13

# Privacy Policy | DSM Publishing

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business.

This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site (“Visitors”) who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register or purchase  to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered or produced by DSM Publishing Limited (collectively, “Services”) (“Authorized Customers”).

**“Personally Identifiable Information”**

This refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual.

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?**  
We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers, the nature and size of the business, and the nature and size of the advertising inventory that the Authorized Customer intends to purchase or sell.

**What organizations are collecting the information?**  
In addition to our direct collection of information, our third party service vendors (such as credit card companies, clearinghouses and banks) who may provide such services as credit, insurance, and escrow services may collect this information from our Visitors and Authorized Customers. We do not control how these third parties use such information, but we do ask them to disclose how they use personal information provided to them from Visitors and Authorized Customers. Some of these third parties may be intermediaries that act solely as links in the distribution chain, and do not store, retain, or use the information given to them.

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?**  
We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Authorized Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information.

**With whom may this information may be shared?**  
Personally Identifiable Information about Authorized Customers may be shared with other Authorized Customers who wish to evaluate potential transactions with other Authorized Customers. We may share aggregated information about our Visitors, including the demographics of our Visitors and Authorized Customers, with our affiliated agencies and third party vendors. We also offer the opportunity to “opt out” of receiving information or being contacted by us or by any agency acting on our behalf.

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?**  
Personally Identifiable Information collected by DSM Publishing Limited is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties or employees of DSM Publishing Limited, except for use as indicated above.

**What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?**  
Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us at [info@dsm-publishing.com](mailto:info@dsm-publishing.com)

**Are Cookies Used on the Site?**  
Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We may use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. For example, if an Authorized Customer is logged on and the site is unused for more than 10 minutes, we will automatically log the Authorized Customer off.

**What Partners or Service Providers have access to Personally Identifiable Information from Visitors and/or Authorised Customers on the Site?**  
DSM Publishing Limited has entered into and will continue to enter into partnerships and other affiliations with a number of vendors. Such vendors may have access to certain Personally Identifiable Information on a need to know basis for evaluating Authorized Customers for service eligibility.

Our privacy policy does not cover their collection or use of this information.

**Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information to Comply with Law.**

We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information in order to comply with a court order or subpoena or a request from a law enforcement agency to release information. We will also disclose Personally Identifiable Information when reasonably necessary to protect the safety of our Visitors and Authorized Customers.

**How does the Site keep Personally Identifiable Information secure?**  
All of our employees are familiar with our security policy and practices. The Personally Identifiable Information of our Visitors and Authorized Customers is only accessible to a limited number of qualified employees who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. We audit our security systems and processes on a regular basis. Sensitive information, such as credit card numbers or social security numbers, is protected by encryption protocols, which has been set in place to protect information sent over the Internet. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable to Visitors or Authorized Customers for any such occurrences.

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites, as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

**Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website, as well as other sites on the Internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies, you may visit the Google Ad and Content Network Privacy Policy at the following url:

Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users’ activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies. **DSM Publishing** has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

**Collection of Personal Information  
**When visiting **DSM Publishing** , the IP address used to access the site will be logged, along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links to Third Party Websites  
**We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement  
**The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of **DSM Publishing** , then please do not hesitate to contact me at **[info@dsm-publishing.com](mailto:info@dsm-publishing.com "mailto:info@dsm-publishing.com").**

Be Sociable, Share!

  *
